给我来点番茄酱吧
Squeeze a little more ketchup on it, would you, buddy?
但如果你矜持点冷静点
However, if you hang back and stay cool...
女孩就会给你自动送上门
...the women come to you.
当然我不是在指"你"  不过  你应该明白我的理论了
Well, not to you specifically, but you get the theory.
是啊  我又不蠢  只是理论上是个父亲
Yeah, I'm not stupid. Just physically repellent...
又不懂得如何去爱
...and inherently unlovable.
别跟我抬杠  我是想教你点经验
Don't get snippy with me. I'm trying to teach you something.
我想要这一整个
Hey, I agreed to one.
杰克  如果你吃完饭了 干吗不开始做点作业
If you're finished with dinner, get started on homework.
我还饿着呢  他吃光了我的薯条
I'm still hungry.  He ate all my fries.
你做完作业可以吃点冰激凌
You can have ice cream when you've done your homework.